Blake Stefansen



linkedin.com/in/blake-stefansen



https://bstefansen.github.io/Portfolio/



bstefansen11@gmail.com

Summary

University of Florida graduate with a passion for technology and the natural world. I specialize in JavaScript and also have experience with GIS products, Python, SQL, and Photoshop

Take a look at my portfolio, and let's get in touch! ##https://bstefansen.github.io/Portfolio/

Experience



Associate Field Geologist

TERRA-COM Environmental Consulting, Inc.

May 2019 - Jun 2019 (2 months)

Collaborated with geologists in preparation of site assessments, data evaluation, HASP's, and report writing. Executed groundwater sampling field services compliant with FDEP regulations.

Office Assistant

Florida Credit Union

Jan 2016 - Apr 2019 (3 years 4 months)

Launched first annual cost analysis report of office supplies, informing senior management of decisions for optimizing annual savings. Developed and managed ordering systems for company supplies, streamlining ordering procedures for company branches and departments. Reduced vendor pricing of office supplies. Drafted and optimized procedures for diverse office tasks. Supervised inventory of corporate office to enhance workflow for office personnel.



Customer Service Representative

Walgreens

Oct 2015 - Dec 2015 (3 months)

Managed the front register and interacted with customers. Responsibilities included maintaining receipts, answering incoming phone requests, giving appropriate change, requesting price checks, and ringing up sales.

Education



UF University of Florida

Certificate, Geospatial Information Analysis (GIS)

2019 - 2020



University of Florida

Bachelor's degree, Geology 2018 - 2020



S_F Santa Fe College

Associate of Arts - AA, Geology 2017 - 2018

Licenses & Certifications

| \wedge | |
|----------|---|
| SAFETY | ١ |
| 14. 1951 | |

40-hour OSHA HAZWOPER Online - Safety Unlimited, Inc.

Issued May 2019 - Expires May 2020

- (A) Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp
- (A) JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures freeCodeCamp
- (A) Front End Libraries freeCodeCamp
- (A) APIs and Microservices freeCodeCamp
- (A) Data Visualization freeCodeCamp
- (A) Information Security and Quality Assurance freeCodeCamp
- (A) Full Stack freeCodeCamp

Honors & Awards

Honors Graduate - Santa Fe College 2018

Charles L. Blount Scholarship - Santa Fe College

Florida Bright Futures Scholarship - Florida Department of Education 2017

Florida Credit Union Scholarship - Florida Credit Union 2017

The Education Foundation Senior Scholarship - Alachua County Public Schools 2017

Skills

JavaScript • React.js • Node.js • Web Development • Data Visualization • Geographic Information Systems (GIS) • SQL • MongoDB • Google Analytics • Python (Programming Language)